Gabriel Antelo | Curriculum Vitae

Sanchez de Bustamante, 731, Buenos Aires, Argentina

Undergraduate computer science master completing the final year of a bachelor's degree. Experience coding and programming accordingly with the criteria defined for each given technology assigned. Good predisposition for new technologies, great working team skills, proactive, resolutive and a big capacity to adapt to any environment.

Previous Employment

Fantommers S.R.L.

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

January 2016-August 2018

.NET Developer, client: Cencosud

Web development using ASP.NET Framework in C# and JavaScript.

Query management in SQL Server.

Angular4 Developer, client: Cencosud

Unit-testing development.

Legacy code maintainer.

Fantommers S.R.L.

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

July 2017–August 2018

I participated in the development and maintaining of the Cencosud's call center web app (a single page application).

Angular5 front-end based and .NET + SQLServer backend.

I was in charge of this company's side project by myself replacing the previous (and original) developer.

Travtion S.R.L. Remote

Angular2+ Developer

September 2018-March 2019

Maintainer of Travtion Solutions Backoffice Frontend.

This included the development of a series of graphical reports, legacy code bugfixing and several other new requirements.

I was also involved in their PHP and JavaScript-based front-end which sometimes required support.

Southworks Buenos Aires

NET Developer. Client: Microsoft

April 2019-Current

Involved in the creation of a new project requiring health check services and telemetry data for the upcoming Windows Virtual Desktop service by Microsoft.

Currently using several design patterns such as repository, composition, dependency injection, factory, bridge, and so on.

Education

Academic Qualifications.....

FCElyA - Universidad Nacional de Rosario
Computer Science (Masters degree),

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina 2013–2019

Notable Projects....

• 4th year project: 'Development of a tiger compiler in Haskell'

I was part of a 2-person project which consisted in creating a tiger compiler in Haskell. This required strong team-working skills and high technical ability. (see https://gitlab.com/DavidGiordana/TigerHaskell)

o 3rd year individual project: 'Concurrent data file system'

This challenging project took place over the entirety of my third year. It required excellent planning and organisational skills, and the ability to teach myself an entirely new and complex subject. The project consisted in implementing a concurrent data file system both in C and Erlang languages, using linux. (see https://github.com/gabriel1536/Emotion98.3, ReadMe in progress)

- o **4th year project:** 'Development of a embedded language for regular expressions analysis' In the 4th year of my course I spent a semester completing a project for parsing and compiling regular expressions. It consisted in creating finite state machines by any browser (supporting javascript) and translating it to haskell language with the 'Haste' compiler for the GHC-based Haskell to JavaScript compiler. (see https://github.com/gabriel1536/Tp-Alp)
- Personal little project: 'Markov chains based BOT for twitter'
 Simple program written in JavaScript that takes any user given tweets, creates a single .txt database and generates arbitrary text based on markov chains probabilities, then posts it as a tweet in a given interval. (see https://github.com/gabriel1536/Bots This has a pending refactor)

Technical and Personal skills

- **Programming Languages:** Proficient in: C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, Haskell, JQuery, Python Also basic ability with: Assembly, Erlang, R.
- o **Industry Software Skills:** Photoshop (Intermediate), Adobe Illustrator (Intermediate), Matlab (Int), Most MS Office products, LATEX.
- Other Software Skills: Machine Learning, currently ongoing course by Udemy: https://www.udemy.com/share/100034BkEcdF5VQXQ=/
- o General Business Skills: Good presentation skills, Works well in a team.
- Other: Can write well organised and structured reports.

Interests and extra-curricular activity

- o I studied for about 3 years musical theory and can play both guitar and piano.
- o I have lots of friends and consider myself a funny but serious guy, and I'm able to easily make new ones!
- o I am also an avid runner, getting up to 10kms twice a week.

References

 $\verb| O Julia Acuña - HR responsible in Fantommers. \\ \verb| https://www.linkedin.com/in/majuliaacuña/. \\ | \\$